Kari-chan, you came to the aquarium.
カリちゃん、水族館に来たね
Yay!
やったー
Look at this.
見てこれ
It's so blue.
めっちゃ青いぞ
Do you like fish?
お魚好きですか?
I like fish.
お魚好きです
like?
好き?
like.
好き
Kari-chan's face is so cute.
カリちゃん顔すごい可愛い
Is it true?
本当ですか?
It's beautiful.
綺麗やなー
綺 麗
It's soothing.
癒されますね
癒されます
amazing.
すごい
There's a stingray.
エイがいるな
What's that big?
あれ何あのデカいの?
Is it a shark?
サメか?
Aren't you scared?
怖くないの?
怖くないんだ?
It would be scary if you were in the ocean and that happened.
海の中に入っててあれがあったら怖いでしょ
That's scary.
それは怖い
Is that scary?
それは怖い?
Hikari-chan is so pure.
ヒカリちゃんすごいピュアだねー
Is it pure?
ピュアですか?
A lot of purity comes out from my whole body.
全身からピュアがいっぱい出てる
The water is clear and beautiful.
水が透明で綺麗だね
If it were me, I'd eat it.
俺だったら食うもんねー
If I were inside this.
この 中にいたら
This guy came, this guy.
こいつ来た、こいつ
It's a large group.
大群です
You're so dignified.
君、堂々としてるねー
Try to make eye contact.
目合わしてみて
Glare.
睨めっこ
It doesn't move at all.
全然動かない
It didn't move.
動かなかった
But it's cute, and I feel attached to it.
でも可愛い、なんか愛着がかかってます
yes?
そう?
Do you like that?
そういうの好き?
like.
好き
cute.
可愛い
Hey, this is cute.
ね、これ可愛いね
cute.
可愛い
Are you sleeping?
寝てんのかな?
That doesn't mean it doesn't move.
動かないってことは
Hikari-chan has an amazing sense of transparency.
ヒカリちゃん、ものすごい透明感
Transparency.
透明感
It's not completely transparent.
透明感半端ないです
Like Nemo.
ニモみたいな
Akama?
赤間?
Isn't Akama here?
赤間いません?
which one?
どれ?
It comes in white or black.
白か黒のしますね
It doesn't come out.
出てこない
That’s it, right?
あれでしょ?
The one who betrays me.
裏切るやつね
That's what I saw.
いたな、そんなやつ
It's pure white.
真っ白だねー
Hello.
こんにちは
Hikari-chan is so cute.
ヒカリちゃん、可愛いね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Hikari-chan is so charming.
すごい愛嬌あるね、ヒカリちゃんは
Is it true?
本当ですか?
She smiles and goes for two, so cute.
笑顔で2個行く、可愛いね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
How many centimeters tall?
身長何センチ?
It is 152 cm.
152センチです
It's 152.
152なんだ
It's small.
ちっちゃいね
小さめです
hey.
ね
What kind of man do you like?
男はどういう人が好きなの?
I like kind people.
優しい人が好きです
kind person?
優しい人?
I'm kind too though.
俺も優しいけど
Are you kind?
優しいですか?
You're kind.
優しいよ
Don't you really care about looks?
見た目はそんな気にしないの?
I don't care about appearance at all.
見た目は全然気にしないです
That's right.
そうなんだ
Looks like it's really popular.
すごいモテそうだね
Looks like it's somewhere like Zaga.
なんとかザガとかに居そうな
He's a good looking kid.
ルックスの子じゃん
You say that a lot, right?
よ く言われるでしょ?
This is often said.
よく言われます
That's amazing.
すごいよ
Not all children in this world are told things well.
世の中の子、みんなよく言われるわけじゃないからね
Who is your boyfriend now?
今、彼氏は?
I don't have a boyfriend.
彼氏いないです
Why aren't you there?
なんでいないの?
why?
なんで?
I can't find the person I love.
好きな人ができなくて
That's right.
そうなの
But you're coming, man.
でも、寄ってくるでしょ、男は
What do you think?
どうなんですかね?
I'm not aware of it.
自覚はしてないです
自覚してないんだ
I think it's better to be aware of it.
自覚した方がいいと思う
I think it's coming very close.
すげー寄ってきてると思う
I guess so.
そうかな
Isn't that the time now?
今、そういう時期じゃないの?
It's not that time.
そういう時期じゃないです
That's right.
そうなんだ
So what are you doing alone?
じゃあ、一人で何してるの?
I'm lazing around at home.
お家でゴロゴロしてます
Lounging around at home?
お家でゴロゴロ?
He's a lazy man.
暇人だね
What are you doing lying around?
ゴロゴロして何してるの?
Did you watch a movie?
映画見たり?
Watch movies.
映画見たり
Also, I look at SNS.
あと、SNS見たり
Instagram?
インスタグラム?
that's right.
そうです
What kind of person do you see?
どういう人と見るの?
What kind of people watch it?
どういう人の見るの?
Instagram?
インスタ?
There may be a lot of fashion people.
ファッション系の人が多いかもしれない
Are you of the same type as me?
自分と同じ系とか?
oh yeah.
そうそう
It's like a sensor system.
センサ系みたいな
It's like that for all the gals.
ギャル系とかそんなみんなそうだもんね
I don't see it.
見ないね
How many boyfriends have you had so far?
今まで彼氏何人くらいいたの?
I have two boyfriends.
彼氏は2人です
There's only two of us.
2人しかいないんだ
yes.
はい
You've been protecting it quite a bit.
結構守ってきてるね
I agree.
そうですね
Is it an all-girls school?
女子校だったりとか?
that's right.
そうです
It was an all-girls school.
女子校でした
That's right.
そうなんだ
I agree with that, a little bit.
それと納得だね、ちょっとね
So, what's your experience with sex?
じゃあ、エッチした経験は?
Number of experienced people.
経験人数
The number of experienced persons is 1.
経験人数は1人です
Is there only one person?
1人しかいないの?
yes.
はい
That's amazing.
すごいね
It's extremely rare these days.
めちゃくちゃレアだね、今の時
1 person has experience.
経験人数1人は
I see.
そっか
2 handsome men?
2人目大丈夫?
Such perverted men.
こんな変態な男たち
It will be stolen though.
奪われちゃうけどね
I'm a little nervous, but it's okay.
ちょっと緊張してるけど大丈夫です
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
I'm nervous, after all.
緊張してるもんね、やっぱりね
She's cute even when she's nervous.
緊張してるとこも可愛いけど
thank you.
ありがとうございます
I see.
そっか
So stand up for a moment.
じゃあちょっと立ってみて
The style is nice too.
スタイルもいいね
Sailor uniforms look great on you.
セーラー服超似合うし
Yay!
やったー
Well then, please take off your mask.
じゃあその、マスクちょっと取ってみて
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Take it slow.
ゆっくりね
So cute.
めっちゃ可愛い
You have such a cute smile.
すごい笑顔可愛いね
This is popular.
これモテるよ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Would you like to walk around Shibuya?
渋谷とか歩いてみ?
I don't think more than 10 people can call.
10人くらい超かけられんじゃねえかな、
this.
これ
So cute.
すごい可愛い
There are many more confessed people, right?
告白された人数はもっといっぱいいるでしょ?
Maybe even if I count, I'm not uncounting.
たぶん数えても数えてなくてないんですよ
I'm not counting.
数えてないんだ
There are so many that I can't count anymore.
もう数えきれないくらいだね
That's right.
そっかそっか
I see.
なるほどね
Look back a little.
ちょっと後ろ向いてみて
This hair is also shiny.
これ髪もツヤツヤ
My cuticle isn't dead at all.
キューティクルが全然死んでないよ
100% survived.
100%生き残ってるね
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Why is your skin so white?
なんでそんな肌白いの?
I'm conscious.
意識してます
意 識してるんだ
Do you mean don't get sunburned?
日焼けしないようにってこと?
Avoid exposure to the sun.
日に当たらないように
That's right.
そうなんだ
Don't you go out much?
あんま外出ない?
It doesn't come out and it's a great sunscreen.
出ないし、めっちゃ日焼け止めになってます
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Otherwise, you won't be able to maintain this white skin.
じゃないとこの美白は保てないんだね
As expected.
や っぱりね
Look, your skin is incredibly transparent.
ほ ら、すごい透明感だもん、肌が
She's so beautiful.
めちゃめちゃ美人です
So you hate summer?
そしたら夏嫌いか
I don't like summer a little.
夏ちょっと苦手です
weak point?
苦手?
I hate sunburn.
日焼けが嫌いだ
I hate sweating.
汗かくのが嫌いだ
Yes, I'm sweating.
はい、汗かく
I don't like either of them.
どっちも嫌だんだ
Do you like winter?
冬は好き?
It's cold, but it makes your skin peel.
寒いけど肌が剥くれるから
That's right.
そっかそっか
If it's this white, you'll want to protect it.
こんだけ白かったら守りたくなるよね
He's the complete opposite of me.
俺と全くの真逆だもんね
It's so white.
すごい白い
My hands are clean too.
手も綺麗だし
Well then, I'd like you to take it off a little at a time.
じゃあそれちょっとずつ脱いでもらおうかな
good?
いい?
Take a picture.
撮っちゃって
It's embarrassing though.
恥ずかしいけど
do my best?
頑張る?
Yes, I'll do my best.
はい、頑張ります
Will you try your best?
頑張るか
Kuro-chan, please take off your sailor suit for a moment.
黒ちゃん、セーラー服をちょっと脱がしてみて
From that ribbon.
そのリボンから
Take it off slowly.
ゆっくり脱がしてあげて
Look at Kuro-chan's face.
見て、黒ちゃんこの顔
Great cleaning.
すごい清掃
It's really cute though.
めちゃくちゃ可愛いけど
The second man is a celestial mask like this.
2人目の男がこんな天体仮面
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Kuro-chan, please relieve your tension.
黒ちゃん緊張をほぐしちゃってね、
Properly.
ちゃんとね
It's really transparent.
ほんと透明感すごいわ
Don't make Kuro-chan suffer.
黒ちゃん苦しめちゃダメだよ
I was just saying hmmm.
今ふーんって言ってたの
It's seriously white.
マジで真っ白やん
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
body.
体
Amazing.
すご
Aren't your boobs big?
おっぱいも大きくない?
No, that's not true.
いやいや、そんなことない
How many cups?
何カップ?
It's C.
Cです
There's more.
もっとあるよ
It looks bigger.
見た目もっと大きいよね
It seems to be around D.
Dぐらいありそうな
No, no.
いや いや
Turn around.
後ろ向いて
It also has a nice waist.
ちゃんとくびれもあって
Look over here.
こっち振り見てみ
So cute.
すごい可愛い
Would you like to see the breasts of such a cute girl?
こんな可愛い子のおっぱい見ちゃう?
Don't tell her to hurry while you're slowly teasing her.
ゆっくり焦らしながら、焦ってばって言っちゃダメだよ
Can I see it?
見ていい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
You can see my boobs.
おっぱい見られちゃうね
Beautiful breasts.
綺麗なおっぱい
It looks like it hasn't been touched at all.
全然触られてなさそうな
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It got photographed.
撮られちゃったね
Her face is so cute.
顔がすごい可愛い
Looks like Hiro Sezuzu.
ヒロセズズみたい
Yes, that's what I'm told.
うん、言われます
Are you told?
言われる?
Erotic?
エロ?
Kuro-chan, look at her breasts.
クロちゃんツンツンしてみて、おっぱい
Just Tsuntsun, just Tsuntsun.
ツンツンだけだよ、ツンツンだけ
Are you jiggling?
プルプルしてる?
The opposition was also sharp.
反対もツンツンして
The needles are amazing.
針がすごいもんね
Then go sit there next time.
じゃあ次にそこに座ってこな
Take care of your boredom.
退屈割りしてこな
Close your legs.
足閉じて
Open your legs slowly.
ゆっくり足開いて
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Yeah.
うん
Cute pants.
可愛いパンツ
Try opening Botgar.
ボットガーって開いてみて
Is that the limit?
それ限界なの?
Kuro-chan, role model, role model.
クロちゃん、お手本、お手本
Finish the model.
お手本仕上げて
I can go a little longer.
もうちょっといけるよね
Those are pure white pants.
真っ白なパンツだね
What's under here?
この下に何あるの?
this.
これ
Do I have to say it?
言わなきゃダメですか?
I have to say it.
言わなきゃダメ
Pussy.
おまんこ
Do you have a pussy?
おまんこあるの?
Seriously?
マジか
I'm really curious.
すげえ気になる
So let's take this off slowly.
じゃあこれゆっくり脱いでみようか
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Take off your clothes.
脱いでこな
Did you take it off?
脱いちゃった?
Take all this.
これ全部取って
A very beautiful pink.
めっちゃ綺麗なピンク
This is a pussy that hasn't been played with.
お手遊ばれてないおまんこだね、これは
Completely.
完全に
Let's open it up a little more.
ちょっともっと開いてみ
Huh?
あれ?
Is that the only thing you can open?
それしか開けないの?
それしか開けない?
I can go a little longer.
もうちょっといけるよね
Kuro-chan, role model.
クロちゃん、お手本
Seino.
せーの
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Come out with me more.
もっと付き出して
yes.
そう
Perfect, Kuro-chan, this is it.
完璧、クロちゃん、これ
I have to open it.
開かないとだね
oh yeah.
そうそう
Keep it when you can't open it, Kuro-chan.
開けない時キープして、クロちゃん
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
I understand.
分かる
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいよね
It might be embarrassing.
恥ずかしいかも
It's so pale.
すげえ淡い
Looks like an idol.
アイドルみたい
This is an idol's pussy.
アイドルのおまんこだよ、これ
Bright pink.
真っピンク
The picture was taken all the way to the back.
奥まで撮られちゃったね
To the deepest part.
一番奥まで
Here, take a look at your face.
ほら、顔映してごらん
Dejama software.
デジャマのソフト
My pussy is a bit damp.
ちょっとでもなんかおまんこ湿ってるよ
I guess I got a little excited about being photographed.
若干撮られて興奮しちゃってんじゃん
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいよ
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Kuro-chan, open your mouth even more.
クロちゃん、もっといっぱい開いて
That's a really beautiful pussy.
本当に綺麗なおまんこだね
You can see all the way to the bottom of the hole.
穴の一番奥まで見えるよ
cute.
かわいい
Then, if there are four,
そしたら、 今度4つの場合、
I put my hands there, my feet and knees,
そ こに手ついて、 足も膝もそう、
Throw the scout now, expose your ass,
スカウトを今投げて、 お尻丸出しにして、
Your butt is also white.
お 尻も白いね
Stick your butt out here,
お尻こっちに突き出して、
Even her butt hole is fully visible.
お 尻の穴まで丸見え
Hold it with both hands and open it as wide as you can.
自分で両手で持って、 ガッと思いっきり開いて
I could see inside her pussy.
おまんこの中まで見えちゃった
Very erotic.
めっちゃエロい
Keep Soma.
ソマはキープね
Soma, look this way.
ソマはこっち向いてみて
That's erotic.
エロいね
Okay then.
じゃあいいよ
Also take pictures of the lighting.
照明も撮って
Hikari-chan, your pussy has been photographed a lot.
ヒカリちゃん、 いっぱいおまんこ撮られちゃったね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I could see everything inside.
中まで全部見えちゃった
Also the butt hole.
お尻の穴も
You looked embarrassed.
恥ずかしい顔してたね
It was embarrassing.
恥ずかしかったです
It's so cute.
かわいいんだもんなに
I have to take lots of pictures.
いっぱい撮んなきゃ
Kuba-chan, with your cute lips,
クバちゃん、 このかわいくちびりに、
Let's just give it a try.
ちょっとチュってやってみよっか
copper?
どう?
cute.
かわいい
soft?
柔らかい?
It's so soft.
すっごい柔らかい
Try it again.
もう一回やってみ
Then let's do it longer
それじゃあもっと長くやってごら
yeah.
ん
That's a really naughty position, Hikari.
す っごいエッチな位置するね、ヒカリ
Chan.
ちゃん
A very deep kiss.
す っごい濃厚な ディーフキス
Hikari-chan, try licking it out.
ヒカリちゃん、ぺろぺろやって出してみ
Please lick here.
ここ舐めてごらん
Hikari-chan, lick it.
ヒ カ リちゃん、ぺろぺろ
I'll lick it gently.
優しく舐めてあげる
Suck it, Hikari-chan's ass.
吸ってあげな、ヒカリちゃんの尻
Hey, Seacro-chan.
おい、シークロちゃん
copper?
どう?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Sea Kuro-chan, take a look.
シ ー クロちゃん、見てごらん
I'm sloppy here too.
ここもぺろぺろしちゃって
Make lots of noise.
いっぱい音出して
Hikari-chan, look here.
ヒカリちゃん、こっち見てごらん
Make your face look like you're feeling it.
感じてる顔にして
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Seacro-chan, please put all of your breasts in your mouth.
シークロちゃん、もっとおっぱい全部口入れて
Hikari-chan has a naughty voice.
ヒカリちゃん、エッチな声出てるよ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Seacro-chan, you need to lick me a lot too.
シークロちゃん、こっちもいっぱい舐めてあげないと
Your breasts were eaten.
おっぱい食べられちゃったね
It's all in Seacro-chan's mouth.
全部入ってるよ、シークロちゃんの口の中に
Breasts.
お っぱい
Do you understand?
わかる?
Seacro-chan licks her armpits too.
シークロちゃん、脇も舐めちゃう
The sides too.
脇も
armpit.
脇の下
Have you ever been licked?
舐められたことある?
armpit.
脇の下
Isn't there?
ないの?
It's my first experience.
初体験だね
Yes, don't be shy if you take the plunge.
そう、思い切ってあげても恥ずかしがらずに
Can I lick it?
舐めていい?
Yeah.
うん
You looked so perverted.
す げー変態な顔したね
copper?
どう?
Spitting and licking for the first time?
初吐き舐める?
It feels weird.
変な感じ
Does it feel a little good?
ちょっと気持ちいい?
It was a mixture of embarrassment and pleasure.
恥ずかしさと気持ちよさが混ざってね
You're a little sweaty.
ちょっと汗ばんでるね
Seacro-chan, please lick me clean.
シークロちゃん、きれいに舐めてあげて
Seacro-chan, you licked this too.
シークロちゃん、こっちも舐めたね
sea ​​black
シ ークロ
Chan, did you lick it clean?
ちゃん、 きれいに舐めた?
Is it clean?
きれいになった?
Aren't you excited?
興奮してきたんじゃない?
already.
もう
Well then, Hikaru-chan, sit there.
じゃあ、ヒカルちゃん、そこに座って
Do you understand anything about this?
これ何でもわかる?
This black one is below.
この黒いのが下の
Below?
下の?
penis.
おちんちん
A black penis?
黒おちんちんか
I understand that, of course.
それはわかるんだ、さすがに
Just pull down your pants.
ちょっとパンツ下ろして
Look, look.
見て見て
There's something about it.
なんかあるね
Now, let's try making a tingling motion with our fingers.
じゃあ、指でさ、ツンツンってやってみましょう
It's getting a little bigger.
ちょっと大きくなってきたね
Yeah, it's getting hard.
うん、固くなってきた
Touch it slowly with your fingers.
ゆっくり指でさわさわして
The skin also peeled off.
皮もズルむけになっちゃった
Try what kind of smell it has.
どんな匂いかかえてみて
What kind of smell?
どんな匂い?
One more time.
もう一回
Doesn't it smell?
匂いしない?
The smell of dick.
ちんちんの匂い
Does it smell like dick?
ちんちんの匂いする?
Seacro-chan, hit her cute face with a punch.
シークロちゃん、可愛い顔にツンツン当てちゃえ
Have you ever been hit in the face?
顔にチンチン当てられたことある?
do not have.
ない
Isn't it?
ないでしょ?
This is also my first experience.
これも初体験
First experience.
初体験
Her nose is high and cute, right?
お鼻は高くて可愛いね、これね
Seacro-chan wants to put it on his nose too.
シークロちゃん、鼻にも当てたいって
Also for your cute nose.
可愛いお鼻にも
She's such a cute girl.
こんな可愛い子いね
I guessed where it felt the most,
一番気持ちいいとこ当てちゃって、
Seacro-chan.
シークロちゃん
Also on the opposite face.
反対の顔にも
Guess it all.
全部当てて
Look ahead?
前見てみ?
Yeah.
うん
Look how big it is.
大きくなってほら
Look how big it has become.
こんな大きくなってほら
Look how big it is.
大きくなってほら
hey.
ね
Well then, let's take out the tongue.
じゃあ、ベロ出してみ
Before that, just Chuu.
その前に、ちゅうだけだ
Please wait for a long time.
ずっとちゅうしてみ
Take out your tongue.
ベロ出してみ
Lick it slowly.
ゆっくり舐めてほら
Seacro-chan, does it feel good?
シークロちゃん、気持ちいい?
Awesome
すっご
stomach.
い
One lap just now, Bellone, Bellone.
さ っき一周、ベローン、ベローンって
Hikaru-chan has a really naughty face.
ヒカルちゃん、すっごいエッチな顔になっている
So let's start from the very root.
じゃあ、一番根元から
Veron to the top.
上の方までベローン
Just take it easy.
ゆ っ く りやってほら
From bottom to top.
下から上まで
Very naughty.
すごいエッチ
It's bigger than your face.
顔より大きいほら
That feels really good.
すっごい気持ちよさそう、それ
Her face is so cute when she's licking it.
チンチン舐めてる顔、すっごい可愛いほら
Hit a lot of pressure points.
いっぱいツボつけてほら
Why don't you make some noise and suck it?
音立てて吸ってみ?
Crackle.
パチパチ
Give me a lot of suck.
いっぱいしゃぶってあげな
Can you see how big it has become?
すんごい大きくなったの分かる?
Hikaru-chan's mouth feels so good,
ヒカルちゃんの口気持ちいいから、
It has become like this.
こんなになっちゃった
Then try to speed it up gradually.
そしたら段々早くしてみる
Take a deep breath and make some noise.
いっぱい吸って音立てて
This is so naughty.
すっごいエッチだよ、これ
I licked it and licked it just now.
さっきもペロペロ舐めて、ペロペロ
While turning everything.
全部回しながら
Feel so good.
いっぱい気持ちよくしな
Yeah.
うん
You like big dicks, right?
でっかいチンチン好きでしょ?
Use your hands while sucking.
しゃぶりながら手も使って
Try it with your hands?
手やといてみ?
Why don't you take out your tongue?
ベロ出してみ?
The tongue is really tongue out and more.
ベロはすごくベロ出してもっと
Hold your head.
頭を持って
Fill your mouth with dick.
お 口の中チンチンでいっぱいにしなほら
Yeah.
うん
Kurushi?
くるし?
Full of dicks?
チンチンでいっぱい?
I'm really greedy and I'm in it, you see.
すっごい欲張で入ってるよ、ほら
It's hitting me on the cheek, Chinch.
ほっぺいに当たってるよ、チンチ
hmm.
ン
Take a look at Iku Rachan, chin chin.
いく らちゃん見してみ、チンチン
Hold it close to your face and see.
顔に近づけて、ほら
It's bigger than my face, look.
自分の顔よりでっかいよ、ほら
Ah, nice.
あ、いいね
Chin Chin, that was really good.
チンチン、すんごいよかったね
It's a big deal.
せっかくなっちゃってね
Well then, this time it's Hikari-chan.
じゃあ、今度はヒカリちゃん
Shall we go to bed?
ベッド行こうか
Sit further back.
もっと奥に座ってほら
About the middle.
真ん中ぐらい
Hikari-chan, come next to me.
ヒカリちゃん、隣に来て
Well, chew it again.
じゃあ、もう一回チューしてほら
Let's both of them cum more.
もっと二人ともペロ出して
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Lick each other.
舐め合いな
If you say it's amazing, I'll check it out.
すごい言ったらチューするね
Just go to sleep.
そんまに寝てほら
Your eyes are round and cute.
お目目、くりくりで可愛いね
Do your breasts feel good?
おっぱい気持ちいい?
Yeah.
うん
There are two people, right?
2人もでしょ?
Don't lick it.
舐めないでね
Please lick me more naughty.
もっといっぱいエッチに舐めてほら
Stand up even more.
もっともっと立てて
delicious?
おいしい?
Kuro-chan.
クロちゃん
Take off your skirt.
スカート脱がして
Can I use it as a spadaka?
スパダカにしていい?
Abune.
あぶね
Can I look at your pussy again?
またマンコ見ていい?
Yeah.
うん
Let's open it to the chest area.
胸地に開いてみましょ
It's so beautiful.
めちゃくちゃ綺麗だよ
Kuro-chan, open to your limits.
クロちゃん、限界まで開いて
All the pussy.
おマンコ全部
Up to the butt hole.
お尻の穴まで
So beautiful.
すーごい綺麗
It's bright pink.
真っピンクだよ
Ask them to see more.
く りもっと見てもらう
Naughty chest.
エッチなくり
Kuro-chan, let me give you a little chew.
クロちゃん、ちょっとチューしてもらう
So that you can see it with your face sideways.
顔を横にして見えるように
Kuri-chan, does it feel good?
くりちゃん、気持ちいい?
Yeah.
うん
Lick it all off your tongue.
舌から全部舐めて
Everything from the tongue.
舌から全部
Keep your feelings down.
お前の気持ちを伏してあげて
Yeah.
うん
A lot more.
も っといっぱい
nine
ク
Have them suck the entire rim.
リ ームいっぱい吸ってあげてもらう
Choo-choo.
チューチュー
Put everything into this hole.
この穴に全部入れて
Let it go all the way inside.
奥まで入れてもらう
Stir it inside.
中でかき回して
Kuro-chan's tongue is full.
クロちゃんの舌いっぱい
Get it all in.
全部入っちゃってよ
Did you put everything in there, Kuro-chan?
全部入れた、クロちゃん?
Now, put it all in.
さあ、全部入れて
Kuro-chan, I want to clean everything.
クロちゃん、全部きれいにしたいな
Everything up to the butt hole.
お尻の穴まで全部
You've never been teased in a place like this, right?
こんなところ、舐められたことないでしょ?
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Let me lick you a lot.
いっぱい舐めてもらう
Kuro-chan, just put it in your ass first.
クロちゃん、お尻に先っちょ入れちゃえばよ
It's in there, you know?
入ってんの、わかる?
Yeah.
うん
Gar-chan, do you understand?
ガーちゃん、わかる?
I understand.
わかる
Black
ク ロ
Chan, look.
ちゃん、 見て
Kuro-chan,
クロちゃん、
Then, try inserting your finger into this hole.
そ したら、この穴、ちょっと指入れてみ
It's slow.
ゆっくりだよ
Isn't it too small to fit in?
狭くて入んじゃね?
Did you enter?
入った?
Once inside, spread it out.
入ったら広げてみせよ
Touch your eyes where they feel good.
目の気持ちいいとこ、触ってあげな
Dog, you got your finger in there.
わんこ、指入っちゃったね
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It feels good there.
そこ気持ちいいんだよ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Kuro-chan, please rub it more.
クロちゃん、もっとこすってあげな
feeling
気持ち
good.
いい
It's all in, you see.
ツ ボツボ入ってるよ、ほら
My butt is sagging.
お尻垂れてきた
You're wet, dog.
濡れ濡れだよ、わんこ
Hey, do you know that you're wet?
ねえ、わかる自分で濡れてる?
I'm talking pichapichai.
ぴちゃぴちゃいってるよ
It felt so good that I got wet.
気持ちくて濡れちゃったんだよ
Kuro-chan, take a look, Manjiru.
クロちゃん、見してみ、まんじる、
There you go.
それほら
This is so hot.
こんなテッカテカ
It's so wet.
すっごい濡れてるよ
Kuro-chan, you look like you're about to feel even better.
クロちゃん、もっと気持ちよくなりそうな顔してるな
Can I use the toy?
おもちゃ使っていい?
good?
いい?
I'm going.
行っちゃうよ
Then.
そしたら
Kuro-chan, look.
クロちゃん、ほら
If it feels good, run slowly.
気持ちいいとこ、ゆっくり走れば
Look.
ほら
Etcher, the white one came out.
エッチャー、白いの出てきたね
Does that feel good?
それ、気持ちよい?
Yeah.
うん
Ah, white.
あ、白い
Etcher is coming out from inside.
中からエッチャー、出てきてるよ
Where does it feel good?
どこ、気持ちよい?
clean.
クリーン
Clean, feel good?
クリーン、気持ちよい?
Clean, it's coming out, does it feel good?
クリーン、出てきてるな、気持ちよい?
I have a pussy.
おまんこがあるんだよ
Your fingers are crunchy, it feels good, right?
指がクリクリ、気持ちよいでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
what up?
どうした?
Yeah.
うん
Does it feel good?
気持ちよい?
Yeah.
うん
Show me?
見せてみ?
Yeah.
うん
Clean, I hate your pussy.
クリーン、行ったまんこ嫌いだよ
Look.
ほ ら
Clippinpin, look.
クリピンピン、ほら
Look, my chestnut is standing like this.
ほら、クリこんな立ってるよ
Isn't this grilled food also available?
こっちの焼きも出てるでしょ?
Let me show you the face of my pussy.
おまんこ、行った顔見せてもらう
Yeah.
うん
I went.
行っちゃった
I stroked the entire back of it.
その後ろ全部撫でた
It was beautifully done.
綺麗にできたな
I still had my face closed.
まだ顔閉めてもらった
Everything is now beautiful.
全部綺麗になった
It was so naughty now.
すごいエッチだったよ、今
Bar-chan.
バルちゃん
Right.
じゃん
That's dangerous.
やばいやつ
OK
Something dangerous.
なんかやばいやつ
Ahaha.
あはは
What do you think?
どうかな?
That's dangerous, right?
やばいでしょ?
I'm surprised.
びっくりだよ
My pussy is so small.
おまんこ、ちっちゃいから
Pussy.
おまんこ
Yeah?
うん?
Pussy like this.
こうやっておまんこ
Pussy.
おまんこ
I went in alone.
ひとりに入っちゃったね
Do you understand?
わかる?
Are you in?
入ってんの
It's all in there.
すぼすぼ入ってんの
Wake me up a little early.
ちょっと早く起こしてね
There, there.
そこ、そこ
There, that's it.
そこ、ついてあんの
I think it feels good.
気持ちいいと思う
Show me your chest.
くりも見せてほら
Look, I'm sucking it in, cunt.
ほら、吸い込んじゃってるよ、おまんこ
Your chest feels good too, right?
くりも気持ちいいでしょ
Are you going?
行っちゃうの?
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
It was so naughty, Hikari-chan.
すんごいエッチだったよ、ひかりちゃん
Well then, Kuru-chan, let's take turns.
じゃあ、くるちゃん、交代
Try this again.
これ、ちんちんまたツンツンしてみて
Just lick it by chance
たまたまなめてごら
yeah.
ん
Have you ever licked it?
そ こ、なめたことある?
do not have?
ない?
copper?
どう?
A strange feeling?
不思議な感触?
I tried licking it all
全部なめてみたもと
too.
も
Do you happen to try putting it in your mouth?
た またま口の中に入れてみる?
enter?
入る?
Did you eat it?
食べた?
You're doing something really naughty right now.
すんごいエッチなことしてるね、今ね
Shake the tongue from below.
下からベロを振って
Give me a lot of tongue.
ベロいっぱい出して
Spit out, spit.
ツバ出してみ、ツバ
It's better to keep getting bigger.
どんどん大きくなってきたほうがいい
Make it dirty with your spit.
い っぱいツバで汚してあげて
Even deeper.
もっと一番奥まで
You're working really hard to get it all the way in.
すんごい頑張って奥まで入れてるね
What do you think, Kuru-chan?
くるちゃん、どう?
Do it sooner.
もっと早くして
While making noise.
音立てながら
Apparently he doesn't like spit.
ツバ嫌らしい
Have you grown up?
大きくなった?
Let me show you.
見せてごらん
Spit on it and do it with your hands.
ツバ垂らして手でやって
Tease the tip a lot.
先っぽいっぱいいじめてあげて
Are you sluggish?
ネレネレしてる?
I'm sluggish.
ネレネレしてる
It's starting to look like it's tipped.
先っぽいぱんぱんになってきた
Yo.
よ
Jubojubo.
ジ ュボジュボして
Spit dripping all over
ツバ垂らしていっぱ
stomach.
い
Let's jubojubo more.
も っとジュボジュボして
Insert it all the way in.
一番奥まで入れてね
To the point where it hurts.
苦しいところまで
Is it really painful?
すごく苦しいの?
Stop at a difficult point.
苦しいところでストップ
Hikari-chan, follow me.
ひ か りちゃん、ついて
Are you getting this far?
ここまで当たってる?
Don't you want to include this big one?
このでっかいのも入れたいんじゃない?
Hika
ひか
Ri-chan, then come here.
り ちゃん、そしたらこっちに
Shall I put it in your pussy?
おまんこ入れよっか
I wonder if this will fit.
入るかな、これ
I wonder if I can go in?
入るかな
Try climbing on it.
上乗ってみて
Put it in slowly.
ゆっくり入れるんだよ
I'm absorbed in it.
めり込んでる
My pussy.
お ま んこちっちゃ
Wow, it came in great.
うわぁ、すごい入ったね
Isn't it tough?
きついんじゃない?
How about Hikari-chan?
ひかりちゃんどう?
tight?
きつい?
Isn't it full?
ぱんぱんじゃないの?
Look, it's up to my eyes.
ほら、目元まで入ってる
Yo.
よ
Does it feel good?
気 持ちいい?
Does your penis feel good?
ちんちん気持ちいい?
It feels good.
気持ちいいんだよ
Second penis.
2人目のちんちん
With such a perverted mask.
こんな変態仮面と
Rub it all over your pussy and see.
おまんこいっぱいこすりつけてほら、
Chin chin.
ちんちん
There's so much in it, you see.
すごいずぼずぼ入ってるよ、ほら
Hikari's pussy.
ひかりちゃんのおまんこ
Does Hikari-chan feel good?
ひかりちゃん気持ちいい?
The pussy is Hikari-chan.
おまんこが、ひかりちゃん
narrow?
狭い?
Then, can you become Yumuji on this?
そしたらさ、 この上でゆむじになれる?
I've never done it though.
やったことないけど
Shall we try it?
やってみるか?
Challenge.
チャレンジ
Can you do a bitch pose?
ビッチなポーズできるかな?
It's the one that hits you deep inside.
それ一番奥までズボッと刺さるやつだよ
Is it stuck?
刺さってる?
Properly?
ちゃんと?
I'm happy that it came from underneath Kuro-chan.
黒ちゃんの下からついたのに幸せ
This pussy looks tight.
おまんこきつそうだね、これ
Look this way.
こっち向いてほら
I'll take it from behind.
後ろから入ってるとこ取ってあげる
Look, there's a huge hole in it.
ほら、すごいズボッが入ってるよ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Come on, go deeper.
ほら、もっと奥までついて
Here you go, chewing.
ほら、チューしながら
Please follow Kuro-chan a lot and make her feel comfortable.
黒ちゃんいっぱいついて気持ちよくしてあげな
Hikari-chan's home
ひかりちゃんのほ
and others.
ら
Give me more of it.
も っとペロ出して
Both of you should cum more.
2人とももっとペロ出して
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Make yourself feel good.
気持ちよくして
Hikari-chan.
ひかりちゃん
Can I make a more naughty pose?
もっとエッチなポーズ出していい?
good?
いい?
Then take out Kuro-chan.
じゃあ黒ちゃん抜いてさ
Opposition.
反対
On top of this is an M letter facing backwards.
この上に後ろ向きでM字だよ
You've never done it, right?
やったことないでしょ?
There are many first-time representatives today.
初代表多いね、今日はね
Kuro-chan, do it.
黒ちゃん、やって
Why do I hate it?
なんで嫌いかな?
So I have them put a chinch in it.
それでチンチ入れてもらう
enter?
入る?
Then move behind you.
そしたら手後ろについて
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
A very naughty pose.
すごいエッチなポーズ
Would you like me to move your hips?
腰動かしてもらう?
Kuro-chan, follow me slowly.
黒ちゃんゆっくりついて
Let me follow you slowly.
ゆっくり追いにしてもらう
I'm taking a chestnut bottle.
くりびんびん取ってるよ
It has a lot of particles in it.
すごい粒々入ってるよ
Look, naughty Poe.
ほら、エッチなポー
Z.
ズ
What's going on with your pussy now?
お まんこどうなってんの今?
It's full of dicks, isn't it?
チンチンでいっぱいでしょ?
I want you to go deeper inside.
もっといっぱい奥までついてもらう
Put it all the way in.
奥までいっぱい入れてこい
Kuro-chan, please follow me again.
黒ちゃん、ほらもう一回ついて
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
It's better to have as many of those pleasant parts as possible.
その気持ちいいところいっぱいついたほうがいいんだ
Kuro-chan, hurry up.
黒ちゃんもっと早く
Put your foot out and see.
足を出してほら
Come early.
早くついて
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Just come forward.
そのまま前へおいで
Kuro-chan, let's have sex slowly.
黒ちゃんゆっくりエッチについてほら
Get it wet.
濡らして
Get it wet with spittle.
ツバでほら濡らして
Feel it all inside your pussy.
おまんこの中いっぱい感じて
Stick to it and feel good.
くりついてあげて気持ちよく
Your pussy feels good, right?
おまんこ気持ちいいんでしょ?
Such a cute butt.
こんな可愛いお尻
This one has all the dick in it.
チンチン全部入っちゃったこれ
I just left, okay.
さっきいっちゃったね、まとも
To.
に
With a pussy?
お まんこと?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
I'm sure you'll get a lot of them.
いっぱいついてもらうじゃん
Follow me a lot.
い っぱいついて
Kuro-chan, come on, please follow me a lot.
黒ちゃんほら、いっぱいついてあげて
Until it feels the most comfortable.
一番気持ちよくまで
Let's make your pussy as wet as possible.
いっぱいおまんこ濡らしてごらん
Try to get it wet.
ぬれぬれにしてごらん
I want you to put a lot of dick in me.
チンチンいっぱい入れてもらいな
I'll give you lots of cock.
チンチンがいっぱいついてあげる
I'll give you the most comfortable part in the back.
奥の一番気持ちいいとこいっぱいついてあげる
While making a lot of noise.
ねちょねちょ音立てながら
Your pussy is full of dick.
おまんこチンチンでいっぱいだね
Hold Kuro-chan's arm.
黒ちゃん腕を持って
It's slow at first.
最初はゆっくりだよ
Follow me to the most comfortable part.
一番奥の気持ちいいとこついてあげな
Have lots of sex.
いっぱい行っちゃうセックスして
Don't tell me your pussy feels good.
おまんこ気持ちいいでって言うな
My pussy feels so good.
おまんこ気持ちいい
I'll tell you to feel good.
気持ちいいでって言うわ
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
Please follow me more.
もっとついてくださいって
Please follow me.
ついてください
I've been asked to do it.
頼まれてるよ
Please fill me with dick.
チンチンでいっぱいにしてくださいって
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Can I have you come all the way in once?
奥いっぱいついて一回かしてもらっていい?
That licking is so naughty.
そのなめ方すんごいエッチだね
It'll get bigger soon.
すぐチンチン大きくなっちゃう
Please make me feel good.
いっぱい気持ちよくしてあげて
Kuro-chan is also cocky.
黒 ちゃんもチンチン
A very naughty sound.
すんごいエッチな音
It's really naughty.
ほんとエッチなめるね
It feels good.
気持ちよさそう
slimy chinch
ぬるぬるチンチ
hmm.
ン
Shall I put it in your pussy at the end?
最後 おまんこ入れるか
Would you like me to fill your tight pussy?
きついまんこいっぱい入れてごらん?
It's tough.
きついね
enter?
入る?
Turn around slowly and enter.
ゆっくり向いて入って
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Put your feet in until they are big enough.
足を大きさを大きくまで入れてあげて
Her pussy looks like it's filled with pressure points.
つぼつぼ入ってるようなおまんだな
Can you show me a lot of sex?
いっぱいセックスしてるとこ見せてごらん?
Does it feel good here?
ここ気持ちいいの?
Yeah, it feels good.
うん、気持ちいい
I'm going crazy in my arms
わんじりでチンチンネレネレになってる
Yo.
よ
That's a naughty pussy.
エ ッチなまんこだね
Kuro-chan goes deep once.
黒ちゃん一回奥までパンガンついて
Kuro-chan will fill it up the most and then let it come out on her face.
黒ちゃん一番パンパンに溜めてから顔に出してあげる
Look, it's amazing.
すーごいチンチンパンパンほら
Please show it to your face.
いっぱい顔に出してください
You want me to come out, right?
出してほしいんでしょ?
This pussy felt so good.
このまんこ気持ちよかったんだ
Did it feel good to have so much cock inside?
チンチンいっぱい入れた気持ちよかった?
It took a lot of sperm.
いっぱい精子かかっちゃったね
So cute.
すごいかわいい
It's like Hyousezon.
ヒョウセスゾンみたいな
Hikaru-chan is also clinging to Manjiri.
ヒカルちゃんもまんじりついてるから
I care about everything.
全部気にするんだよ
Understood?
わかった?
Kuro-chan doesn't twitch.
黒ちゃんピクピクしないよ
Look at it from the root.
根元からベラーっとみろ
Everything is easy.
全部なんでもベラベラ
Get smoother from the roots.
もっと根元からベラベラ
Only the tongue is all.
ベロだけ全部
Was it beautifully done?
綺麗にできた?
Well then, last time I licked it all up.
じゃあ 最後さっきっぽペロペロって全部舐めてあ
Get it.
げ て
Hikaru-chan.
ヒカルちゃん
How was your day?
今日どうだった?
I was nervous but it was fun.
緊張したけど楽しかったね
it was fun?
楽しかった?
I was really nervous at first.
すごい最初緊張したもんね
That's so cute.
すごいかわいいね、それ
It was really fun.
どうも楽しかった
it was fun.
楽しかった
See you again.
また会おうね
That's it again.
またそう
Let's play secretly again.
また秘密な遊びしよう
bye bye.
バイバイ